




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ALT&#43;CS Lab</title>
    <link>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content on ALT&#43;CS Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who We Are</title>
      <link>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/people/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/people/index.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/cyber-pipeline/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/cyber-pipeline/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Cyber Pipeline Initiative seeks to broaden participation in computing by assisting Kansas K-12 schools in bringing quality computer science instruction to all Kansas students. Computational thinking and programming are recognized as critical 21st century skills for every career, as the transformative impact of computer technology has come to bear on every aspect of our lives. Wether it be authoring original software, using data mining techniques to analyze the genome of a new bovine virus, creating computer models of the watersheds that recharge the Ogallala aquifer, or programming a drone to overfly a wheat field to assess hail damage, the techniques and skills of computer science have role to play in all Kansans&amp;rsquo; lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scratch Activities</title>
      <link>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/scratch/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/scratch/index.html</guid>
      <description>These activities were developed by the Department of Computer Science at Kansas State University as examples of how computer science can be embedded in interdisciplinary activities and used in elementary and middles school classrooms. All activities provided are released under creative commons licenses and can be adapted to suit your needs.
Have an idea for an activity you would like us to help you develop? Please contact us and let us know!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading Group</title>
      <link>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/reading-group/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/reading-group/index.html</guid>
      <description>This is the homepage of the ALT+CS CS Education Reading Group.
When: Mondays at 1:30 PM (Spring 2024) Where: ALT+CS Lab (DUE 2208) and via Zoom Schedule Date Presenter Paper 1/29/2024 Friday James Sometimes It&amp;rsquo;s Just Sloppiness - Studying Students&amp;rsquo; Programming Errors and Misconceptions 1/22/2024 Russ Feldhausen Exploring CS1 Student&amp;rsquo;s Notions of Code Quality 10/4/2023 Nathan Bean Using Programming to Express Mathematical Ideas 9/13/2023 Russ Feldhausen Engagement and Anonymity in Online Computer Science Course Forums 9/6/2023 Friday James Plagiarism Deterrence in CS1 Through Keystroke Data 8/30/2023 Nathan Bean Neo-Piagetian Theory as a Guide to Curriculum Analysis 8/4/2023 Zach Berard Another Victim of COVID-19: Computer Science Education 7/21/2023 Samatha Ereshi Akkamahadevi Students&amp;rsquo; Initial Course Motivation and Their Achievement and Retention in College CS1 Courses 7/14/2023 Akhil Joshi CS1 Students&amp;rsquo; Perspectives on the Computer Science Gender Gap: Achieving Equity Requires Awareness 7/7/2023 Namratha Kommineni A Fresh Look at Novice Programmers&amp;rsquo; Performance and their Teachers&amp;rsquo; Expectations 6/30/2023 Sai Teja Erukude Examining the Digital Divide between Rural and Urban Schools: Technology Availability, Teachers’ Integration Level and Students’ Perception 6/16/2023 Russ Feldhausen CS0 vs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>