




	
	
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		

	
	
		
		
		

	
	
		
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Who We Are on ALT&#43;CS Lab</title>
    <link>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/people/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Who We Are on ALT&#43;CS Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Josh Weese</title>
      <link>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/people/weeser/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/people/weeser/index.html</guid>
      <description>Josh Weese is one of the ALT+CS Co-Directors and teaches in the Department of Computer Science. His hometown is Macksville Kansas (pop. 471) and he is a graduate of Macksville High School.
View Larger Map Education Ph.D. Computer Science from Kansas State University M.S. Computer Science from Kansas State University B.S. Computer Systems Technology Kansas State University A.S. Computer Systems Technology from Kansas State University </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Bean</title>
      <link>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/people/nhbean/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/people/nhbean/index.html</guid>
      <description> One of the ALT+CS Co-Directors, Nathan teaches in the Department of Computer Science. He hails from Luray Kansas (Pop. 166) and a graduate of Lucas-Luray High School.
View Larger Map Education Ph.D. Curriculum and Instruction - Kansas State University M.S. English (Creative Writing) - Kansas State University M.Sc. Computer Game Programming - University of Abertay Dundee B.S. Computer Science - Kansas State University </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russell Feldhausen</title>
      <link>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/people/russfeld/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:53:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alt-cs-lab.github.io/people/russfeld/index.html</guid>
      <description>Russell Feldhausen is the Director of the Cyber Pipeline and Computational Core programs and teaches in the Department of Computer Science. He is from Frankfort Kansas (pop. 730) and a graduate of Frankfort High School.
View Larger Map Education M.S. Computer Science from Kansas State University B.S. Computer Science from Kansas State University </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>